>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 我想说，就像其他的行动一样，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And I would claim
that just like every other operation,
了解类型是有帮助的。
it is helpful if you
understand what the types are.
和其他的操作一样你得问自己
Like every other operation,
you have to ask yourself,
如果我知道这些类型在这里是否有用
if I know the types,
is coercion here helpful or not?
也许是有用的也许不是
Maybe it is helpful, maybe it isn't.
这是一个关键的分析。
It's a critical analysis.
把讨论从双方面改变是不好的，不可预测的
It shifts the discussion away from
double equals is bad and unpredictable
我想让你做个强制性的比较或者我不想让你这样做吗
to do I wanna allow a coercive
comparison or do I not wanna allow that?
在这件案子里，我这样做是否更有帮助呢 ?
In this particular case,
is it more helpful to me to do so or
对你的帮助减少了吗
is it less helpful?
是否更安全，还是不安全 ?
Is it more safe or is it less safe?
换句话说，你必须是批判的，分析思考的思考者，
In other words, you need to be critical,
analytical thinkers, and
看看你的密码
look at your code.
然后决定你的密码和你不能做的事
And decide what you can know about
your code and what you can't.
基本上是关于双等号和三等的决定
And essentially the decision about
double equals and triple equals
是一个跟踪指示符，表明您是否实际了解程序。
is a trailing indicator of whether
you actually understand your program.
让我再说一次
Let me say that again.
你选择三等同等比不只是因为
Your choice to use triple equals,
it's not just because
有些人在书中写道你应该总是用三等
some guy wrote in a book that you
should always use triple equals.
您选择使用三重等号的实际选择是指后退的指示符
Your actual choice to use triple equals
is a trailing indicator which points back
而你也不知道那种比较的类型
to the fact that you don't know something
about the types in that comparison and so
你必须保护自己
you have to protect yourself.
我的意见是，如果可能的话，最好是把根
And my opinion is, if at all possible,
maybe it would be better to fix the root
问题，即我不知道该比较中的类型是什么。
problem, which is that I don't know
what the types are in this comparison.
太难以预测了太多态了
It's too unpredictable,
it's too polymorphic.
>> Kyle Simpson: 这会导致更好的代码，减少错误，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: That's gonna lead
to better code with fewer bugs,
不管您使用的是双等号还是三重等号。
regardless of whether you use
a double equals or a triple equals.
决定您的类型，从而清楚地显示您的类型。
Deciding what your types are,
making it obvious what those are.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 我们知道这些类型吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So
do we know those types?
让我们看看双等号要做什么
Let's take a look at what
the double equals is going to do
如果类型不同。
if the types are different.
首先，如果类型为空或未定义在任一方上，
First off, if the types are null or
undefined on either side,
这两个子句是成对的，如果 x 为空而 y 未定义或
that's what these two clauses are paired
to say, if x is null and y is undefined or
反之亦然，然后返回 true。
a vice versa, then return true.
换句话说，不值和未定义的值是强制相等的
In other words, the no value and the
undefined value are coercively equal to
以及语言中没有其他值，这就是第 10 条的内容。
each other and to no other values in the
language, which is what clause 10 says.
上面写着退货是假的
It says return false.
NULL 和 undefined 将与此算法中的任何其他子句不匹配，
Null and undefined will not match
any other clauses in this algorithm,
除第 2 及 3 条外
other than clause 2 and 3.
所以这对彼此都是胁迫性的
And so it's only coercive to each other.
我觉得这是一个非常有用的关于 JavaScript 的事实
I find that to be a tremendously
useful fact about JavaScript because,
说实话我不喜欢有两个空值
quite honestly,
I don't like having two empty values.
我觉得这很困惑
I find that to be confusing.
所以我宁愿选择一个空值。
So I would much rather
deal with one empty value.
并且由于 NULL 的类型比未定义的值短，
And since null is shorter
to type than undefined,
我宁愿到处都是空的
I'd rather deal with null everywhere.
并且尽可能地假装没有定义的不存在。
And pretend as much as possible
that undefined doesn't exist.
或者至少假装它们是可以互换的
Or at least pretend that
they're interchangeable.
JavaScript 会对它们进行一些区分，
JavaScript does make some
distinctions between them,
例如缺省值算法。
such as the default value algorithm.
但是，在大多数情况下，您可以选择处理空值和
But, for the most part,
you have the option of treating null and
未定义为通过强制平等无法区分。
undefined as indistinguishable
through coercive equality.
你可以这样做你可以有个工作坊
So you could do a check like this,
you could have a workshop one and
一个研讨会两个，上面有一个专题。
a workshop two, and
there's a topic property on there.
如果设置了主题属性，并且它为空，那么您可以询问该主题属性，或者
You could be asking of that topic property
if it's been set and it's null, or
如果它从未被设定过，或者被设定了，也没有定义。
if it's never been set at all, or
if it's been set and it's too undefined.
你可以试着区分两者但
You could try to distinguish
between those two, but
在几乎所有情况下，我都认为这不是有用的区别。
I would argue in almost all cases,
that's not a useful distinction.
属性是否已创建，并已复位为空，或者
Whether the property was ever created and
has been reset back to null, or
它是否已重新设置为未定义，或者它是否从未创建过。
whether it's been reset back to undefined,
or whether it was never created at all.
这些基本上都是一样的情况，至少我还会说，
Those are basically all the same
condition, or at least I would argue,
这是一种更好的编码方式来对待那些难以区分的人
that's a better way to code,
to treat those as indistinguishable.
所以有一个选择是你写你在第 5 行上做的事情
So one option is for
you to write what you do on lines five and
六，就是用这个三等等于不允许威逼，
six, which is to use this triple equals
that does not allow coercion and
明确检查所有这些情况。
explicitly checks all of those cases.
显式检查 workshop1.topic 为 Null 或者
Explicitly checks that
workshop1.topic is null or
未定义 workshop1.topic ，并且 workshop2 主题的相同。
workshop1.topic is undefined and
the same thing is true of workshop2 topic.
>> Kyle Simpson: 您是否在此处显式地获取任何可读性 ?
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Are you gaining anything
readability-wise by being explicit here?
问自己，读者要不要再笑了 ?
Ask yourself the question if the reader
has benefited from having to juggle
两个空值之间的区别吗
in their head the distinction
between two empty values?
>> Kyle Simpson: 我的断言是不，他们没有受益。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: My assertion is that no,
they are not benefited.
用我们在第 12 和第 13 条上的双等号
And using the double equals like we
do down here on lines 12 and 13,
现在更清楚了
it's far more clear.
它说，不管它是空的还是没有定义的，告诉我它们是否为空。
It says, whether are null or undefined,
tell me if they're empty or not.
告诉我如果他们是这两个空值中的一个
Tell me if they're one of
those two empty values.
顺便说下，我只选了两个小的小熊的矮型。
And by the way, I just picked the shorter
of the two cuz it's less to type.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 好吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Okay?
这是使用强制等式的示例，并且
This is an example of using
coercive equality, and
即便是一些严重地批评过胁迫的人
even some of the staunchest
harshest critics of coercion,
您将在其代码中使用双等号空检查来查找它们。
you will find them using double
equals null checks in their code.
因为它的争议性比其他几个双数相等。
Because it's less controversial than
some of the other double equals usages.
大多数人似乎都没问题
Most people seem to be okay with that.
即使 JFLint 说不不，大多数其他的人都遵守了这些规定。
Even though JFLint says no no, most other
people have those linting rules turned on.
我使用 ESLint ，它是一个令人惊奇的可配置的链接器。
I use ESLint,
it's an amazingly configurable linter.
我确定我和你的规则很不一样
I have a very different rule
set than you do, I'm sure,
cuz 我有很不同的意见，但是我用 ESLint 工具
cuz I have very different opinions,
but I use an ESLint tool and
我打开规则，帮助我编写更好的代码，这就是画家的工作。
I turn on what rules help me write better
code and that's what linters are for.
Linters 是一个帮助你决定是否
Linters are an opinion that
helps you decide whether or
而不是您的代码以这样的方式格式化，或者构造为这样，
not your code is formatted in such a way
where, or structured in such a way,
以避免错误，或者是否可能发生问题。
to avoid bugs or whether it's
likely that a problem will occur.
它不检查您的编程是否正确。
It's not checking if your
programming is correct.
它让你知道你是否做了正确的事
It's giving you an opinion on
whether you've done the right thing.
意见的问题是，每个人都有不同的意见。
The thing about opinions is that
everybody's got different opinions.
所以最好的工具是最可配置的工具
So the best tools are the ones
that are most configurable,
不仅仅是针对个人的意见，而是针对团队的最有效的方式。
not just to individual opinions,
but most effectively for teams.
让团队决定什么是有效的。
Let a team decide what is effective for
them.
在任何程度上，您使用的工具与您的代码共享有关代码的意见
To any extent that you use a tool that
shares an opinion about your code with
您通过对构建过程进行错误处理，在该工具的范围内
you, by way of erroring out your build
process, to the extent that that tool is
无法对其进行配置，以便您能够更有效地完成工作，并且
unable for you to configure it so that you
can get your job done more effectively and
它迫使你改变代码的适应方式
it forces you to change the way
you code to adapt to it,
那么这个工具就没有帮助你，阻碍了你的发展机会。
then that tool is not helping you, it is
hampering your development opportunities.
如果它不够聪明就能理解它在做什么
If it's not smart enough to
understand what it's doing.
比如，我用 ESLint 和 ESLint 的一套很棒的规则
For example, I use ESLint and ESLint's
got a bunch of really great rules in,
但有些规则很幼稚
but it's got some rules
which are pretty naive.
其中一个规则是要处理变量声明
One of those rules has to deal
with variable declarations,
是否允许您先前在作用域中使用变量声明。
whether you're allowed to use a variable
declaration earlier in the scope.
现在我可以明确地说，我们将在我们的范围内回到这个单位，
Now I can clearly say, and we're gonna
come back to this in our unit on scope,
但我可以明确地告诉你我不建议说 A 等于 2
but I can clearly say to you that I
wouldn't recommend saying A equals two and
那么 Var A的情况就很糟糕了
then Var A,
that's a terrible usage of that.
但同样的规则也阻止了我说 A 等于 2
But that same rule that prevents that
also prevents me from saying A equals two
在函数中，如果 var A 不在代码中的函数之上。
inside of a function if the var A isn't
above the function in the code.
这完全不是一回事，但这一工具还不够聪明。
That's not at all the same thing, but
that tool is not at all smart enough to
在作用域限定行为中区分这两个差异。
distinguish those two
differences in scoping behavior.
这条法则让我不再帮我
And that rule gets in my
way instead of helping me.
所以我不使用那条规则
So I don't use that rule.
有关 ESLint 的好消息是您可以编写自己的规则。
Good news about ESLint is you
can write your own rules.
我刚写了我的第一个 ESLint 规则插件。
I actually just wrote my
first ESLint rule plug in.
我们稍后再谈这个问题。
We'll talk about that one
a bit later on the course.